Chantilly, VA 20152 | 412.517.2228 | andrew.noonoo@gmail.com | https://apnoono.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software engineer with over five years of system integration and QA experience supporting various software development projects for government clients. Able to drive development cycle from requirements gathering and planning to delivery. Proven ability to learn new skills quickly and write maintainable, clean code.

- ❖ Java/ES6 Proficient, Python Intermediate
- Knowledge of Data Structures/Algorithms
- Experience /w various DevOps Pipelines

- Linux CLI / VIM / Git Intermediate
- ❖ Great Written and Oral Communication
- ◆ DoD TS/SCI Security Clearance

EXPERIENCE:

Zachary Piper Solutions (Microsoft Vendor)

Infrastructure Engineer, Reston, VA

July 2021 – July 2022

- ❖ Validated integrity of public-facing Azure SQL VM offers as required by internal governance/risk/compliance (GRC) policies by integrating optimistic concurrency control into an Azure Devops pipeline.
- ❖ Achieved 100% parity between public and air gapped Azure SQL VM offers by coordinating with multiple teams within the deployment pipeline.

Novetta

QA/Devops Lead Engineer, Tyson's Corner, VA

April 2018 – July 2021

- ❖ Improved early detection of application defects by driving development of a QA automation pipeline designed to perform Linux system calls, web requests, and Docker image management.
- Installed and configured data center network hardware and power management to maintain a continuous cyber tool development environment.
- ❖ Improved internal organizational knowledge and reduced end-user adoption time by creating workflows, test deliverables, and user guide documentation for each quarterly release.

Accenture

Devops Engineer, Vienna, VA

August 2017 – April 2018

- Enabled DoD medical professionals to focus on patient care sans IT troubleshooting by developing service monitoring scripts in Ruby and leveraging Chef continuous delivery to automate validation and code infrastructure change management within the DoD MHS Genesis production environment.
- ❖ Maintained test automation infrastructure on a daily basis by provisioning core Windows/Linux VMs and updating web app XML to test application components in isolation.

IT Security Consultant, Alexandria, VA

February 2016 – August 2017

- Developed security accreditation documentation and lead enforcement of client Information Assurance policies for a DOD project.
- Configured and managed client hardware valued at greater than \$500K, opened trouble tickets, and communicated network outages.

United States Army

SIGINT / Korean Language Analyst, Various Locations

August 2005 – March 2011

Drafted over 300 summarized intelligence reports, enabling military leaders to make risk framework-based decisions.

EDUCATION:

Columbia University, New York, NY B A East Asian Studies

January 2012 – May 2015